<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<all-pulau xmlns="http://www.around-the-world.com/"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.around-the-world.com/ file:/F:/Vocation-spot-in-indonesia/xml/Pulau.xsd">
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P001">
        <Nama_pulau>Jawa</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Mount Bromo</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Mount Bromo is one of the active volcanoes in Indonesia, 
            precisely in East Java and covers four districts namely Probolinggo, Pasuruan, Lumajang and Malang. 
            As the volcano is still active, 
            so Bromo-known tourist destination in East Java and almost never empty every day.</Small-Description>
        <Description>Status = still active
            H = 2,392 meters above sea level
            has its vast sea of ​​sand = (- / +) 5,300 hectares
            
            Mount Bromo in Probolinggo travel icon known as the most beautiful and most visited. The word "Bromo" comes from the word "Brahma" is one of the Gods of Hinduism. 
            Mount Bromo is not as large as other volcanoes in Indonesia but the scenery is fabulous Bromo all. 
            The beauty of Mount Bromo outstanding makes tourists amazed.
            
            Communities around Mount Bromo will celebrate the festival Yadnya Kasada or Kasodo annually by describing the offerings such as vegetables, 
            chicken, and the money will be offered to the gods and thrown into the crater of Mount Bromo. 
            As a form of gratitude to the almighty.
            
            Activities Mount Bromo
            
            The eruption in 2004 Mount Bromo erupted in 2004. The eruption resulted in the death of two people because the exposed rocks of volcanic eruptions. 
            The eruption in 2010 On Tuesday, November 23rd, 2010, at 16.30 WIB (Western Indonesia Time), 
            Center for Volcanology and Indonesia Geological Hazard Mitigation (CVGHM) confirmed that 
            the status of activity at Mount Bromo was "alert" because of the increasing activity of 
            tremors and volcanic earthquakes shallow happened on the mountain. 
            The eruption in 2011 The eruption of Mount Bromo on January 22, 2011 05:30 
            made crater of Mount Bromo to not visible) Tengger still active at the end of January 2011, 
            the activities were marked by fluctuations of the ongoing eruption.
        </Description>
        <Last-Description>History Mount Bromo
            
            Antiquity when the kingdom of Majapahit received many attacks from all regions, 
            many natives so confused to find a new place to live until they finally split into 2 parts. 
            One heading to Bali, two to Mount Bromo. Second place is until now have in common is equally embraced Hinduism.
            The name "Tengger" is believed to come from the legend Anteng Roro and Joko Seger. 
            "Teng" is Roro An-name suffix "teng" and "ger" is the suffix of the name of Joko As "ger" and Mount Bromo also believed to be a sacred mountain. 
            Hindu communities call it by the name of Mount Brahma. While the Javanese call it Mount Bromo. Less like that of origin - origin of the legend of Mount Bromo.
            
            The crater of Mount Bromo
            To be able to reach the location of the crater of Mount Bromo travel, 
            from where parki Jeep visitors can use the services of rent a horse or walk approximately 1.5 km to reach the stairs which numbers about 250. 
            The road is impassable sandy and passed the Holy Temple Tribe Tengger commonly functioned to implement Yadya Kasada celebrations or commonly called by the name of Kasodo ceremony, 
            according to legend came from the crater Bromo Tengger volcanic eruptions. With a diameter of approximately 800 meters (north-south) and approximately 600 meters (east-west). 
            While the hazardous area of ​​a circle with a radius of 4 km from the center of the crater of Mount Bromo.
            
            Teletubbies hill savannah Mount Bromo
            Is a desert-savannah commonly called by the name of Mount Bromo Teletubbies hill and surrounded by rows of hills. 
            A natural landscape is perfect, it can be said Mount Bromo has a natural charm which is very comprehensive, 
            ranging from beautiful sunrises, splendor Tourism bromo crater, 
            or caldera sea of ​​desert and grass savannah contained in this field. 
            
            Climbing Mount Bromo
            
            Mount Bromo is the best location in Indonesia to see the sun rising very beautiful and charming. 
            In order to achieve Ascent of Mount Bromo, tourists can use the Bromo jeep rental services to deliver to the tourist sites of interest in Mount Bromo. 
            Depart to the summit of Mount Bromo Pananjakan be done in the early morning at around 03.00 am and the trip can be started from the inn where you stay at Mount Bromo, 
            so you do not miss the sunrise in the tourist area of ​​Mount Bromo.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/bromo.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P002">
        <Nama_pulau>Jawa</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>MONUMEN NASIONAL(MONAS)</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>existing tourist destinations in Indonesia's province of East Java National menyuguhkanMonumen or popularly abbreviated with Monas monument or memorial is as high as 132 meters (433 feet) erected in memory of the resistance and the Indonesian people's struggle for independence from Dutch colonial rule. 
            
            The construction of this monument began on August 17, 1961 under the orders of president Sukarno, and opened to the public on July 12, 1975. This monument crowned with flame-coated gold sheet which symbolizes the spirit of struggle fiery. The National Monument is located right in the center of Merdeka Square, Central Jakarta. 
            Monuments and museums are open every day starting at 08:00 to 15:00 pm. On the last Monday of every month is closed to the public.</Small-Description>
        <Description>History
            After the central government of the Republic of Indonesia returned to Jakarta after previously located in Yogyakarta in 1950 following the recognition of the sovereignty of the Republic of Indonesia by the Dutch government in 1949, President Sukarno began planning the construction of a national monument that is the equivalent of the Eiffel Tower on the ground right in front of the Palace. Monas monument Development aims to commemorate and preserve the Indonesian struggle for independence during the revolution of 1945, in order to continue to inspire patriotism and spirit of the next generation.</Description>
        <Last-Description>At the base of the monument at a depth of 3 meters below ground level, there is the National History Museum Indonesia. Great room museum of history of the national struggle with the size of 80 x 80 meters wide, can accommodate about 500 people visitors. The room is large marble there are 48 dioramas on all four sides and 3 diorama in the middle, so that a total of 51 dioramas. This diorama featuring the history of Indonesia since the pre-history up to the New Order. This diorama dimula from the northeast corner of moving clockwise trace the history of Indonesia; start the pre-history, past ancient empires such as Srivijaya and Majapahit, followed by Europeans during the colonial period that followed the resistance of the pre-independence national hero against the VOC and the Dutch government. Diorama continued until the Indonesian national movement early 20th century, the Japanese occupation, the war of independence and the revolutionary period, until the time of the New Order in the Suharto era.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/Monas.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P003">
        <Nama_pulau>Jawa</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Mount Tangkuban Perahu</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Tangkuban Perahu, or Tangkuban Perahu is one of the mountains which is located in West Java Province, Indonesia. About 20 km to the north of Bandung, with lush pine trees and expanse of tea gardens in the vicinity, Mount Tangkuban Perahu has a height as high as 2,084 meters. Forms of this mountain is Stratovulcano the eruption center that moves from east to west. Rock types are mostly issued by the eruption of lava and sulfur, a mineral which is issued sulfur sulfur, a mineral that was issued when the mountain is not active sulfur vapor. Tangkuban Perahu Mountain area administered by the Corporation of Forestry. Daily average temperature was 17 ° C at noon and 2 ° C at night.
            Mount Tangkuban Perahu has a forest area Dipterokarp Hill, Dipterokarp forest Upper Montane forest, and forest Ericaceous or mountain forests.</Small-Description>
        <Description>MOUNTAIN HISTORICAL BOAT TANGKUBAN BANDUNG
            
            The story of Mount Tangkuban Perahu Bandung is very legendary and full of natural beauty and kontroversial.Di behind the cool and cold of this region, turns attractions in Bandung western save a million mysteries of a case that the writer is a case of incest or incestuous perkawianan the days of yore , which although not yet happened but it is behind the name of a mountain so famous until now.</Description>
        <Last-Description>MOUNTAIN TOUR BOAT TANGKUBAN BANDUNG
            
            Mountain that is still fairly active this is an area of natural attractions of Bandung, which is adjacent to the area lembangs Bandung and also an excellent tourism areas in West Java, because of the natural attractions of the typical mountain that has many unique and of course the beauty of the panorama and the cool air is able to attract a lot number visit of tourists to visit beautiful place is very beautiful on weekends especially when the long holiday season</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/Tangkuban-Perahu.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P004">
        <Nama_pulau>Sumatra</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Lake Toba</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Lake Toba is a tekto-volcanic lake with a length of 100 kilometers and 30 kilometers wide, located in North Sumatra Province, Indonesia. 
            This lake is the largest lake in Indonesia and Southeast Asia. In the middle of this lake there is a volcanic island called Pulau Samosir.</Small-Description>
        <Description>existing tourist destinations in the Indonesian province of East Java is presenting with a height of almost one kilo meters above sea level and surrounded by rows of volcanoes are part of the Barisan Mountains hills make Lake Toba so cool and beautiful. Lots of palm trees and pine thrives around Lake Toba add to the beauty of this lake.
            On the north side of Lake Toba still be found a variety of interesting fauna such as monkeys, orangutans, and several types of monkeys. Meanwhile, in the southern part of Lake Toba there are different types of fauna such as lingur monkeys, tapirs, and ingkir. Surely it is also unique because the lake as if it serves as a dividing line ecology fauna in the north and south of Lake Toba.
            As far as the eye could see, the visible beauty of the lake surrounded by a row of mountains are so beautiful and amazing. Sometimes thick fog enveloped the lake cool and cold. If there is no fog, the curve of Lake Toba is so beautiful to be admired. Yes, Lake Toba like a sea in the middle of the land which is really cool.</Description>
        <Last-Description>In the middle of Lake Toba there is an island that is no less beautiful and amazing that Naidoo. There we can visit some villages and enjoy nature and cultural tourism. Lake Toba and Samosir Island is the heart and the hometown of the Batak.
            To visit Samosir Island, Parapat can through the port that is Port Ajibata. There are several ferries available to take the locals as well as tourists to the Port Tomok in Samosir Island. Even there is also some ferries transporting vehicles such as cars and motorcycles towards Naidoo. Long ferry ride to the island of Samosir about 30 minutes.
            When it reaches Port Tomok in Samosir Island, there are many traders unique souvenirs and typical of Lake Toba Batak land in the area around Port Tomok, Samosir. You can buy T-shirts, crafts and also Ulos at this location if you want to buy souvenirs to take home. We recommend buying souvenirs here because a lot of options that you can buy to take home.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/Lake-Toba.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P005">
        <Nama_pulau>Sumatra</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Nias Island</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Nias (Nias language Tano Niha) is an island located west of the island of Sumatra, Indonesia. The island is inhabited by a majority ethnic Nias (Ono Niha), which still has a megalithic culture. This area is an important tourist attractions like surfing (surfing), traditional houses, dives, fahombo (jump stone).
            Island with an area of 5,625 sq km has a population of 700,000 inhabitants.
            
            This area is the religion of the majority of Protestant Christians. Nias has been split into four counties and one city, namely Nias, South Nias Regency, Nias Barat, North Nias and Gunungsitoli.
        </Small-Description>
        <Description>
            Nias Island lies about 125 km of west Sumatra Island on the Indian Ocean. It is part of North Sumatra Province. The water surround the island is great for sea activities, such as surfing and scuba diving. The people also have curious culture, which will enrich visitor's heart. The island has some prehistoric remains, which built on megalithic Stone Age, and considered came from the oldest megalithic culture in Indonesia.
        </Description>
        <Last-Description>The local call their land as Tano Niha or "land of the People", while the people calls them selves as Ono Noha. Ethnically, the Niasers are involved in to the Ptoto-Malay ethnic who once ever get with the Asian Proto-mongoloid world. Niasers speak a kind of language related to Malagasy. Because of the similarity in languages, custom, body size of the Niasers with the Bataks on Sumatra mainland, it is possible that the Niasers have derived from the Bataks.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/Nias-Island.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P006">
        <Nama_pulau>Sumatra</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Bangka Belitung Island</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Bangka Belitung (Babel abbreviated) is a province of Indonesia which consists of two major islands, the island of Bangka and Belitung islands and small islands such as P. Lepar, P. Pongok, P. and P. Mendanau Selat Nasik, total island which has been named amounted to 470 pieces and only 50 islands are inhabited. Bangka Belitung is located in the eastern part of the island of Sumatra, close to the South Sumatra province. Bangka Belitung is known as the producer of tin, has a beautiful beach and inter-ethnic harmony. The capital of the province is Pangkalpinang.
            The provincial government was ratified on February 9, 2001. After the inauguration Pj. Governor of the Amur Muchasim H., SH (former Secretary General of Ministry of Home Affairs) which marks the commencement of the activity of the provincial government wheel.
            
        </Small-Description>
        <Description>Bangka Strait separates the island of Sumatra and Bangka, while the Gaspar Strait separates the island of Bangka and Belitung. In the northern part of the province there is the South China Sea, the south is the Java Sea and the island of Borneo in the eastern part of the island of Belitung, separated by the Strait of Karimata.
            
            Bangka Belitung Islands formerly part of South Sumatra, but became its own province along with Banten and Gorontalo in 2000. Bangka Belitung Islands was established by Act No. 27 of 2000 on the Establishment of Bangka Belitung Province November 21, 2000 consisting of the District Bangka, Belitung Regency and Pangkalpinang. In 2003 pursuant to Act No. 5 of 2003 dated January 23, 2003 made the regional growth with the addition of four districts namely Bangka Barat, Central Bangka, Bangka Belitung South and East. Bangka Belitung Islands is a regional division of the province of South Sumatra.
            Bangka-Belitung is one of Indonesia provinces. It includes two large islands, Bangka and Belitung, and several smaller ones, which lie east of Sumatra, northeast of South Sumatra province. Bangka Belitung (BABEL) Islands province is the 31st Province in Indonesia, one of the newest provinces. Bangka Belitung get it’s approved as a new province in 2001 separated with south Sumatra. That acknowledgement is because of the people struggle. The region that was a great tin mines, now already to reach the new phase in its life. It provisioned with the beautiful of nature, and the uniquely of culture, Bangka Belitung step to the better future.
        </Description>
        <Last-Description>Supported by the “Serumpun Sabalai” spirit and abundant natural resources, it has been expecting a greater role to speed up the island region's development, namely Bangka regency, Belitung regency and Pangkal Pinang city through cooperation development. That potency of culture and tourism is also supported by its strategic location that can connect with other interesting area. The sea transportation that become the most accessibility in Bangka Belitung Island, is support its economics activities among the Islands.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/belitung.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P007">
        <Nama_pulau>Sumatra</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Lake Kerinci</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Local authorities utilize Kerinci Lake as one of the prime tourist destination for the region of Kerinci. Because many interesting sights that are served such as around Lake Kerinci visitors can see a collection of grouse that berkliaran. Region around Lake Kerinci also can be used as an attractive recreational water such as fishing, swimming, campsites or other activities such as typical culinary travel Kerinci provided by restaurants that surround Lake Kerinci.</Small-Description>
        <Description>If you wish to visit tourist sites Kerinci Lake, you can take advantage of a wide range of facilities and accommodation in Kerinci Area locations. There are several hotels in the district of Kerinci that you can use to stay. If you want to save even more, you can take advantage of existing facilities Area homestay lake at a cost much cheaper than the cost of staying at the hotel.</Description>
        <Last-Description>If you visit the attractions of Lake Kerinci, then do not forget to stop by to various other travel loksai. Area location of this lake, there are so many tourist attractions that are not less interesting. Tourist objects are also quite varied ranging from natural attractions, attractions entertainment, to the culinary attractions.
            
            One of the attractions of nature Area lakeside location you must visit is the Cape Hatta. From Tanjung Hatta, you can witness the beauty of Lake Kerinci more widely. Besides Tanjung Hatta, there are also several other tourist sites such as the Village Seleman, Middle Island Village, and several other attractions. every tourist attraction in this area offers a travel experience that is different from one another.
            
            Once you are satisfied surrounding natural attractions in Kerinci, you can enjoy a variety of typical food of Jambi province in various attractions culinary Area lakeside location. some typical food so we recommend you try is Tojin Nuts, Fish Stew Semah, Rice Payo, Orange Pelompek, Dendengn Beteko, and tea Kayu Aro.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/Danau-Kerinci.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P008">
        <Nama_pulau>Kalimantan</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Melawai Beach</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>If the view of its geographical position facing toward the East, it seems difficult to find a spot to view the sunset in Balikpapan, East Kalimantan. But, assuming it will be broken after you visit Melawai beach is not far from the city center.
            The position of the beach is in a small bay making it as the location of the best sunset view in Balikpapan.
            To get to this beach, you only need to take a 5 minute drive from the city center. Ngesot wrote nyampe. In addition to its sunset views of the slick, you can also see the carrier vessels milling Semayang port. There is also a Pig Island who can go by foot at low tide. 
        </Small-Description>
        <Description>When it was dark, glowing view of the flare gas from oil refinery chimney will accompany the hubbub of the cafes on this beach.
            Melawai beach is still located in the city center, exactly not so far from the complex Pertamina Balikpapan port and on the edge of one of the protocols Balikpapan, Jl Sudirman. proximity to the city center, Balikpapan Center or about 5 minutes to the south. And to get to the location Melawai beach is very convenient for public transport pass which numbered 6 and 3, or you can use a personal vehicle.
        </Description>
        <Last-Description>The uniqueness of this Melawai Beach is at dusk you can sit mat mat while waiting for the sunset and enjoy the view of the ships at anchor were being unloaded at the Port Semayang, or saw the ship sailing in the Gulf of Balikpapan.
            
            It overlooks the beach and Makassar strait as a favorite tourist destination in the downtown area is also a center of food and drinks in the evening. This beach will be more crowded in the afternoon until evening. because a lot of traders who sell food on the waterfront makananya Melawai this month.I'll many young people who come to just hang out here. The beach is also a culinary center of Balikpapan city at night.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/mentawai.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P009">
        <Nama_pulau>Kalimantan</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Tanjung Puting</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Because of deforestation, the survival of orangutans in Borneo increasingly threatened. Fortunately, there is a conservation area that is home to those at Tanjung Puting National Park in Central Kalimantan.</Small-Description>
        <Description> 
            This vast wilderness sanctuary for orangutans eventually become endangered and various other animals.
            Together ranger, into the jungle to meet with orangutan is an experience that awaited. You can see the orangutans that marvelous hanging out while she ate the food provided officers rangers. 
            Some are trained to be more friendly with humans, you know. So, do not be surprised if suddenly there orangutans are toward you.</Description>
        <Last-Description>Tanjung Puting is covered by a complex mosaic of diverse lowland habitats. It contains 3,040 km2 (or 1,174 square miles) of low lying swampy terrain punctuated by blackwater rivers which flow into the Java Sea. At the mouth of these rivers and along the sea coast are found nipa/mangrove swamps. Mangroves teem with animal life. Tanjung Puting also includes tall dry ground tropical rain forest, primarily tropical heath forest, with a canopy of 30 meters (approximately 100 feet) with “emergents” exceeding 50 meters (approximately 165 ft) in height, seasonally inundated peat swamp forest with peat in layers two or more meters (approximately 7 feet) deep, open depression lakes formed by fire, and open areas of abandoned dry rice fields now covered with elephant grass and ferns.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/tanjung-puting.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P010">
        <Nama_pulau>Kalimantan</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Kembang Island</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Forests other interesting attractions you can find in Pulau Kembang. This 50-hectare island is in the middle of the Barito river delta which is formed naturally. This area is a habitat for a herd of long-tailed monkeys and various bird species.</Small-Description>
        <Description>
            That said, the herd is led by the king ape-ape, certainly not Sun Wukong, anyway. But these monkeys sacred by local Chinese citizens. In fact, in the middle of the forest there is a statue of the altar or the white monkey Hanuman. 
            You can reach the island located in Barito Kuala, South Kalimantan by boat motors from Barito river bank.</Description>
        <Last-Description>Flower Island is a habitat for the long-tailed macaques (monkeys) and several species of birds. Flower island region also is one of the attractions that are in the forest area in Barito Kuala.
            
            In the forest area there are altar designated as a place to put the offerings for "keeper" Flower island symbolized by two statues tangible white ape (Hanuman), by the community of ethnic Chinese in Indonesia that have specific vows or vows. A male goat horns gilded normally released into the jungle island of Flowers if a request is successful or fulfilled.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/kembang-island.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P011">
        <Nama_pulau>Papua</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Biak Island</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Biak Island and numfor is a unity that forms the Biak district. Island located in Cenderawasih Bay has many interesting places to visit. In North Biak, there Kampung Amoi is famous for its beautiful landscape. </Small-Description>
        <Description>
            In addition, there is also the Museum of paradise that has many collections in the days of World War II. Do not forget to try the local specialties in Biak. Marapen Cassava is one of them.
            
            Cassava is processed in a manner wrapped in banana leaves and then grilled over coals is a treat that must be enjoyed. There is also Japan IYEN, taro is boiled without seasoning and served with spicy seasoning marine fish. 
            One of the attractions in Biak is the Bird Park and Orchid Garden located in the area Bosnik. There is a collection of birds and plants are quite diverse and complete information. 
            Biak surrounding area, there are many interesting tourist destinations, such as beaches and waterfalls Bosnik Wafsarak located around the island of Biak.</Description>
        <Last-Description>In ancient times, the island of Biak including the territory of the Sultanate of Tidore who divided into 9 districts (uli Shiva). In World War II, the airfield's strategic Japanese Imperial Forces were there as a command base in the Pacific War. US soldiers then take control of the island. On May 29, 1944, inter-tank battles took place in Biak.
            
            Biak belongs to Indonesia from the grip of the Netherlands, along with Irian Jaya (Papua), 1960. In 2005, the Russian government is committed to launch rockets and satellites from Biak Island because of its strategic location and is not far from the ocean.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/biak-island.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P012">
        <Nama_pulau>Papua</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Wafsarak Waterfall</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Located far enough away from the town of Biak, a waterfall that must be taken 2 hours from the city center by car or motorcycle is also located not far from the beach.</Small-Description>
        <Description> 
            Waterfalls are also referred to Warsa waterfall has a height of about 10 meters, although classified ramps, but the view of the waterfall and the rustling of water that greeted us when entering the area very soothing waterfall.
            
            The locals are maintaining the cleanliness of these places, can be seen from the color of bluish waterfalls and cool unspoiled scenery. To enter the waterfall, there is a collection fee per group of 35 thousand rupiah. 
            Come to this waterfall, we were allowed to swim, and enjoy the view of the falls from the top of the hill that is no less beautiful. Of course, with the condition that we do not carelessly throw garbage or littering the area around the waterfall. 
            For the tourists who love waterfalls, of course, many places also gives beauty waterfall tour in Indonesia that must be visited.</Description>
        <Last-Description>The sound of the water falling will make you relax. Moreover, the clear greenish-blue color of river's water will make you want to take a dive. Up to now, one factor why there are few tourists coming here is that the local government does not really advertise or promote this destination. However, that is a benefit as you can now freely enjoy the beauty of the waterfall without the crows. The scenery around of the waterfall is still natural and untouched and, uncommon in Indonesia, you will for sure not find any garbage here lying around as the local people care about their environment.
            
            After you have took a swim and watched the waterfall from close-by, you can climb to the cliff or walk to the top of hill to even get a more better view of this amazing waterfall. Don't forget too to take a look at the close-by beach.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/wafsarak.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
    <DetailPulau ID_PPulau="P013">
        <Nama_pulau>Papua</Nama_pulau>
        <Name_tempat>Raja Ampat Island</Name_tempat>
        <Small-Description>Raja Ampat was originally a unity with Sorong regency, until finally becoming Raja Ampat district in 2004. The islands with beautiful underwater scenery is already known to many local and foreign tourists, and included into one of the world heritage site with the most beautiful scenery in the world , To achieve and take a walk around the island, we could have boarded the ship or stay at one of the resorts on the islands of Raja Ampat.</Small-Description>
        <Description>
            Magnificent place is certainly very popular into tourist attractions that are suitable for young children as well as couples who are want to find a place to honeymoon travel.
            
            Although many divers who makes this island destination choice because it has a lot of coral reefs and marine animals, but also many that can be seen in Raja Ampat apart underwater beauty. One is a white sandy beach, a cluster of karst islands, and also the endemic flora and fauna such as birds of paradise and orchids.
            
            One of the highlights of the island of Raja Ampat is a relic of prehistory. Located in the constellation Misool, there are labeling a hand on the wall of rock. Cap-hand stamp which is believed to be 50,000 years old is very close to sea level and not in the cave. In addition, there is also a legacy of the wrecked aircraft from World War II at Wai island.</Description>
        <Last-Description>The oceanic natural resources around Raja Ampat give it significant potential as a tourist area. Many sources place Raja Ampat as one of their top ten most popular places for diving whilst it retains the number one ranking in terms of underwater biodiversity.
            
            According to Conservation International, marine surveys suggest that the marine life diversity in the Raja Ampat area is the highest recorded on Earth.[3] Diversity is considerably greater than any other area sampled in the Coral Triangle composed of Indonesia, Malaysia, Philippines, Papua New Guinea, Solomon Islands, and East Timor. The Coral Triangle is the heart of the world's coral reef biodiversity, making Raja Ampat quite possibly the richest coral reef ecosystems in the world.</Last-Description>
        <Image>images/raja-ampat.jpg</Image>
    </DetailPulau>
</all-pulau>